Good morning
This is NSB Emergency News
First in the news
People who have decided to join forces
with the monkeys have been sighted in the cities
They have pleged their allegiance to the monkeys,
and there has been a festive mood all over the world
as these people increase in numbers
Government of the monkeys,
by the monkeys,
and for the monkeys!
Hurah for the monkeys!
It appears that the situation is quite chaotic
Next, from Japan
The mysterious creatures that have been vandalizing the cities,
are thought to be from the huge crashed battleship in the ocean
We have a helicopter report from the site
Nonaka-san?
はい
戦艦の墜落現場上空に来ています
海岸から5キロぐらいの地点でしょうか
戦艦は海に沈むことなく海面に漂っていまして
所々に壊れた跡が見られます
そこから緑色の液体か気体のようなものが漏れ出していまして
どうやらあの緑の物体が
謎の生物発生の現況であると考えています
ではないかと思われます
危険ですのでこれ以上戦艦に近づくことはできないんですが
まるで巨大な生物がごめん出ています
海戦に問題が生じているようです
Well it seems we're having some technical difficulties
We will get back to you later with more news
I am Fraya DeVapes,
that was the latest news